Captioning Provided By:
MTV Networks
字幕提供者：
MTV网络
Are ya ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：
是的，是的，船长。
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
Patrick: SpongeBob...
帕特里克：海绵宝宝……
SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
Ooh.
哦。
SpongeBob...
海绵宝宝...
You forgot to tell me
you were leaving.
你忘了告诉我
你要离开了。
Well, Patrick, I...
guess this is...
好吧，帕特里克，我...
猜猜这是...
I'm gonna
miss you, buddy.
我要
想念你，伙计。
Me too, Patrick, me too.
我也是，帕特里克，我也是。
♪ Sun fun island,
it's so fun ♪
♪ 阳光欢乐岛，
太有趣了♪
♪ Sun fun island, here we come ♪
♪ 阳光欢乐岛，我们来了 ♪
♪ Sun fun island... ♪
♪ 阳光乐趣岛... ♪
♪ Sun fun island,
we can't wait ♪
♪ 阳光欢乐岛，
我们等不及了♪
:
♪ La-la, la, la, la ♪
：
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
♪ La-la, la, la... ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦…… ♪
Oh, Patrick, if I had
only known how hard
哦，帕特里克，如果我有的话
只知道有多难
not saying good-bye could be.
不说再见也可以。
Well, see you later, bud.
好吧，再见，伙计。
Patrick, that's it.
帕特里克，就是这样。
You can come with
me to summer camp.
你可以带着
我去夏令营。
Then I never have
to say good-bye.
那我就从来没有
说再见。
Summer camp?
夏令营？
But I'm not even ready yet.
但我还没准备好。
How 'bout now?
现在怎么样？
This stuff is just
my carry-on, porter.
这东西只是
我的随身行李，搬运工。
The rest of my things
are right over there.
我剩下的东西
就在那里。
Patrick: Whee...
帕特里克：呼……
Oh, and porter... Thanks.
哦，还有波特……谢谢。
Campers: ♪ Sun fun island,
we can't wait ♪
露营者：♪ 阳光乐趣岛，
我们等不及了♪
Boy, that looks like a boring
boat to be on, huh, guys?
男孩，这看起来很无聊
伙计们，要上船吗？
Guys?
伙计们？
Welcome to Inferno Island.
欢迎来到地狱岛。
Yay!
耶！
What in the seven seas just
assaulted my ear drums?
七大洋里有什么
侵犯了我的耳膜？
Could that have been an
unrequested sound off?
那会不会是一个
未经请求的声音关闭？
Well, it must have
been my imagination?
嗯，它一定有
是我的想象吗？
And you can all thank
your lucky stars
你们都可以感谢
你的幸运星
that I have a very
active imagination
我有一个非常
活跃的想象力
because it so happens
that it is my sworn duty
因为事情就是这样发生的
这是我的宣誓职责
to think of fun things to do
想想有趣的事情要做
with the trash that
society has thrown away.
与垃圾
社会已经抛弃了。
I always prefer to recycle.
我总是更喜欢回收。
Holy fish paste.
圣鱼酱。
We got ourselves a couple
of rabble rousers.
我们给自己找了一对
煽动者。
What's your name, son?
儿子，你叫什么名字？
SpongeBob SquarePants.
海绵宝宝。
And are you a rabble rouser?
你是一个煽动者吗？
Funny you should ask.
有趣的是你应该问。
Once I...
有一次我...
because you sure
look might tasty.
因为你确定
看起来可能很好吃。
And it's too soon
after breakfast
而且还为时过早
早餐后
for me to want to chew
somebody's head off.
让我想要咀嚼
有人掉头了。
Actually, I am a little hungry.
其实我有点饿了。
Hungry?
饥饿的？
Barney, fetch these two
poor hungry souls a snack.
巴尼，把这两个人拿来
可怜饥饿的灵魂的零食。
On the double!
上双！
Both: Mmm...
两人：嗯……
Oh, these guys are tough.
哦，这些家伙太难了。
The food coma
is setting in.
食物昏迷
正在设置。
Yeah, I could use a nap.
是的，我可以小睡一下。
Did you say a nap?
你说午睡吗？
Well, I know the perfect
place for you two
嗯，我知道完美的
你们两个的地方
to go digest that meal.
去消化那顿饭。
...couple days in the hole
never hurt anybody.
...在洞里呆了几天
永远不要伤害任何人。
This camp is very upscale.
这个营地非常高档。
I had no idea
they had a hot tub.
我不知道
他们有一个热水浴缸。
Man: Three days later.
男：三天后。
All right, let 'em out.
好吧，让他们出去吧。
Now pay attention, worms.
现在注意了，虫子们。
Watch the way they
crawl out on their bellies
观察他们的方式
趴着爬出来
begging for mercy.
乞求怜悯。
And see what's waiting for you
看看有什么在等着你
next time you foul up the same
way these two did.
下次你犯同样的错误
这两个人就是这么做的。
It was quite
an enjoyable soak...
这是相当
一次愉快的浸泡...
That is until
this guy got thirsty
也就是直到
这家伙渴了
and decided to drink
the bath water.
并决定喝酒
洗澡水。
Not bad.
不错。
Except for this
aftertaste.
除了这个
回味。
Shut your traps,
all of you.
关闭你的陷阱，
你们所有人。
Because of that little outburst
因为那小小的爆发
I am going to treat you all
我会好好对待你们所有人
to an activity so
heart-wrenchingly boring
到一个活动所以
无聊得令人心碎
and physically exhausting
和体力消耗
that it is guaranteed
to render your souls
这是有保证的
来渲染你的灵魂
broken beyond repair.
破损无法修复。
Yay.
耶。
This is a pretty fun
camp game, huh, Patrick?
这是一个非常有趣的
营地游戏，嗯，帕特里克？
Yeah.
是的。
It's made even more
还做了更多
fun and challenging
by the fact that we're
有趣且具有挑战性
事实上我们是
wearing these
heavy ankle weights.
穿着这些
脚踝的重量很重。
Warden: Good night, ladies.
典狱长：晚安，女士们。
Man: My corns
won't stop ringing.
男：我的鸡眼
不会停止响铃。
Man 2: I miss my
rubber ducky.
男2：我想念我的
橡皮鸭。
What's wrong, SpongeBob?
怎么了，海绵宝宝？
The other campers
just aren't having
as much fun as you and me.
其他营员
只是没有
和你我一样有趣。
If only we could think of
some sort of group activity
如果我们能想到
某种团体活动
that we could all do together.
我们都可以一起做。
Then we'd all be having the same
amount of fun as each other.
那么我们都会有同样的经历
彼此都充满乐趣。
Good night.
晚安。
That's it.
就是这样。
We'll show him
we can be self-starters.
我们将向他展示
我们可以成为自我启动者。
Rise and shine.
崛起并闪耀。
Now...
现在...
Which one of you vile
你们哪一个卑鄙
low-down
低下的
foul, miserable wretched swine
肮脏的、可怜的、可怜的猪
left this pathetic worthless,
horrid, meaningless...
让这个可怜的东西毫无价值，
可怕的、无意义的...
Uh, abomination?
呃，可恶？
Who said that?
谁说的？
Me, sir.
我，先生。
What is the meaning
of this thing?
有什么意义
这件事的？
It's a play.
这是一场戏。
For our amusement
and inspiration.
为了我们的娱乐
和灵感。
Hmm...
唔...
: Of course.
： 当然。
Well, then...
嗯，那么...
I'll watch your play.
我会看你的戏。
And I will enjoy every
act of your pathetic
我会享受每一个
你可悲的行为
meaningless,
ridiculous production.
无意义，
可笑的生产。
You know why?
你知道为什么吗？
Uh... Because you cherish
呃……因为你珍惜
the fine art
of thespianism?
美术
戏剧主义？
Because it'll be the
last act you'll ever perform
因为这将是
你将表演的最后一幕
in your pathetic lives.
在你可悲的生活中。
So get to it.
所以开始吧。
And I'd better
be truly entertained.
而且我最好
得到真正的娱乐。
Cool.
凉爽的。
Kid's wasting his time.
孩子在浪费时间。
All done.
全部完成。
You thinkin' what
I'm thinkin'?
你在想什么
我在想？
Uh...
呃...
It's a boat,
you simpleton.
这是一条船，
你这个傻瓜。
What do boats do?
船有什么作用？
Uh... Make smoke.
呃……抽烟。
No, you knucklehead.
不，你这个笨蛋。
They float...
他们漂浮...
Away from this island
远离这个岛
with all of us onboard.
我们所有人都在船上。
Now here's the plan.
现在这是计划。
Hey, buddy,
you need some help?
嘿，伙计，
你需要帮助吗？
Really?
真的吗？
Sure.
当然。
Man: Opening night.
男：开幕之夜。
Aye, for jib's men.
是的，为了吉布的人。
What forceth blow the merry
winds of Galilee?
是什么力量吹起欢乐
加利利的风？
Get ready.
准备。
Huh... Oh.
呃...哦。
♪ 'Tis we ♪
♪ 这就是我们 ♪
♪ Here to sing the song ♪
♪ 来唱歌吧 ♪
♪ Of maritime camaraderie ♪
♪ 海上友情 ♪
♪ Together ♪
♪ 一起 ♪
Together!
一起！
♪ Together ♪
♪ 一起 ♪
Together!
一起！
♪ Together ♪
♪ 一起 ♪
♪ To-geth-er ♪
♪ 一起来 ♪
♪ Like a boat ♪
♪ 像一条船 ♪
♪ Upon the sea ♪
♪ 在海上 ♪
Together.
一起。
♪ In happy camaraderie ♪
♪ 快乐的友情 ♪
Together.
一起。
♪ That's the way
it ought to be ♪
♪ 就是这样
应该是♪
Together.
一起。
♪ Just you ♪
♪ 只有你 ♪
♪ And you ♪
♪ 还有你 ♪
All: ♪ And me... ♪
全体：♪ 而我...♪
Together.
一起。
♪ Together ♪
♪ 一起 ♪
Together.
一起。
I've never seen anything
so beautiful in my...
我从未见过任何东西
如此美丽在我的...
My...
我的...
OK, let's do it.
好吧，我们开始吧。
SpongeBob: Uh, hey, guys,
what are you doing?
海绵宝宝：呃，嘿，伙计们，
你在做什么？
We're breakin'
out of here, that's what.
我们正在打破
离开这里，就是这样。
Escaping.
逃跑。
Oh, and thanks for the
convincing stage craft.
哦，谢谢你
令人信服的舞台工艺。
Encore, encore, encore.
安可，安可，安可。
Do... Do it again.
做……再做一次。
What the...
什么...
Turn the ship around.
把船调转方向。
Man: I can't swim.
男：我不会游泳。
I'm stumped.
我很困惑。
I can't even
begin to imagine
我什至不能
开始想象
a punishment appropriate for
what has happened here tonight.
适当的惩罚
今晚这里发生了什么事。
Words cannot attempt to
describe the disgusting
言语无法尝试
形容令人厌恶的
vile, the, the...
卑鄙的，那个，那个……
the complete disregard
for the storied tradition
of musical theater.
完全无视
为了传奇的传统
的音乐剧。
So starting this very moment
所以从这一刻开始
every one of you "subprotozoas"
你们每一个“亚原生动物”
will be sentenced to...
将被判处...
Man: Ahoy... Hello.
男：啊嘿……你好。
Yoo-hoo.
哟吼。
What in the name of...
以什么名义...
For Neptune's sake, man
看在海王星的份上，伙计
speak the King's English.
说国王的英语。
I'm...
我是...
I'm Camp Counselor Krauss
from Sun Fun Island.
我是营地辅导员克劳斯
来自阳光岛。
You're who, what?
你是谁，什么？
Well, I was doing roll call
嗯，我当时正在点名
and discovered one of
my Sun Funners was missing.
并发现了其中之一
我的 Sun Funner 不见了。
I came to take him
back with me...
我来接他
和我一起回来...
...a SpongeBob SquarePants?
...海绵宝宝？
Me, me...
我，我……
Enough.
足够的。
So tell me counselor
那么请告诉我辅导员
just what do they do on
your Sunny Funny Island?
他们只是做什么
你的阳光有趣岛吗？
Well, we make macaroni art.
好吧，我们制作通心粉艺术。
Egad.
埃加德。
And we sing campfire songs.
我们唱篝火歌曲。
Ach.
阿赫。
Oh, and we help
and support each other.
哦，我们帮忙
并互相支持。
Stop!
停止！
These heinous activities
这些令人发指的活动
sound like torture
too severe for even
听起来像酷刑
太严重了，甚至
the lowest, filthiest,
undeserving...
最低级的、最肮脏的、
不值得...
Wait a minute...
等一下...
I have a brilliant idea.
我有一个绝妙的主意。
Oh, that is
very good, Bruiser.
哦，那就是
非常好，布鲁斯。
Patrick?
帕特里克？
You first.
你先。
I...
我...
I liked the other
island better.
我喜欢另一个
岛更好。
Me too.
我也是。
What the...
什么...
Whoa, there,
calm down.
哇，那里，
冷静下来。
Tell me what happened.
告诉我发生了什么事。
SpongeBob and I are being
chased by a savage beast.
海绵宝宝和我正在
被野兽追赶。
And he's gonna eat us.
他会吃掉我们。
Oh, no, he ain't.
哦，不，他不是。
There it is!
就在那里！
:
This little guy?
：
这个小家伙？
Why he's just
a harmless little cricket.
为什么他只是
一只无害的小蟋蟀。
He's a land creature
just like me.
他是陆地生物
就像我一样。
Poor thing
must've got lost.
可怜的东西
一定是迷路了。
He's not gonna
hurt you...
他不会
伤害你...
See?
看？
Oh, let's get you back home,
little fella.
噢，让我们送你回家吧
小家伙。
There you go.
就这样吧。
See, that wasn't nothing
to be afraid of, huh, guys?
看吧，这并不是什么
害怕吧，伙计们？
I don't have time for this.
我没有时间做这个。
I'm late for my survival
training camp.
我为了生存而迟到了
训练营。
Survival training camp...
生存训练营...
Patrick and I  love  camping.
帕特里克和我喜欢露营。
Can we come?
我们可以来吗？
This ain't no ordinary
camping trip.
这不是普通的
露营旅行。
I go out into the wild
我到野外去
armed only with my bare hands
只用我的双手武装
my quick wits
我的机智
this harpoon...
这鱼叉...
and 65 pounds of dynamite.
和 65 磅炸药。
Out in the wild
在野外
it's eat or be eaten.
它是吃或被吃。
You have to be willing
to do anything
你必须愿意
做任何事
when you're alone
in the wild.
当你独自一人时
在野外。
You two wouldn't
last a single day.
你们两个不会
持续一天。
Hey...
嘿...
We would so.
我们愿意这样。
I'll have you know
that just the other day
我会让你知道
就在前几天
Squidward commented on
our survival skills.
章鱼哥评论了
我们的生存技能。
You two are harder to
get rid of than cockroaches.
你们两个更难
比蟑螂更能除掉。
Thank you,
Squidward.
谢谢你，
章鱼哥。
Why aren't these
things working?
为什么不是这些
事情有效吗？
No way, guys.
没办法，伙计们。
This is a serious trip for
hardcore survivalists only.
这是一次严肃的旅行
仅限铁杆生存主义者。
But Sandy...
但桑迪...
No.
不。
Ohh...
哦...
Shh...
嘘...
We'll show Sandy we're
as tough as she is.
我们会向桑迪展示我们
和她一样坚强。
Oh, I guess the
road smoothed out.
哦，我猜是
道路变得平坦。
Ahh...
啊...
That was a close
one, Patrick.
那是一个关闭
一，帕特里克。
We were almost left in the
wilderness without Sandy.
我们几乎被留在了
没有桑迪的荒野。
And nobody would've known
where to find us.
没有人会知道
在哪里可以找到我们。
Weird... There's
a door back here, too?
奇怪……有
后面还有门吗？
No, Patrick, no!
不，帕特里克，不！
Whoa...
哇...
Sandy, wait...
桑迪，等等……
Sandy...
沙...
Sandy!
沙！
Well, at least we have
food, shelter and water.
好吧，至少我们有
食物、住所和水。
I'll pitch the tent
while you start a campfire.
我来搭帐篷
当你生起篝火时。
Then when we're all settled
然后当我们都安定下来
I'll cook us up some grub.
我给我们煮点食物。
OK, Patrick, we're all set.
好的，帕特里克，我们都准备好了。
We got fresh water,
a rugged tent for shelter...
我们得到了淡水，
一个坚固的帐篷来避难...
And a nice fire
to keep us warm.
还有一团漂亮的火
让我们保持温暖。
Hey, where'd you
get the fire wood?
嘿，你在哪儿
得到木柴吗？
SpongeBob:  :
You burned our food supply?
海绵宝宝：：
你烧了我们的食物供应吗？
Oh, no, quick, quick,
put it out with something.
噢，不，快点，快点，
用东西把它灭掉。
Ahh, ahh, ahh...
啊啊啊啊啊……
Hey, Patrick, nice job.
嘿，帕特里克，干得好。
Whew.
呼。
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
Well, we burned our food
好吧，我们烧掉了食物
ruined our tent
and lost all our water.
毁了我们的帐篷
并失去了所有的水。
Patrick, we are gonna need to
use our razor-sharp quick wits
帕特里克，我们需要
运用我们敏锐的机智
if we're gonna make it
out of here alive.
如果我们能成功的话
活着离开这里。
Got ya.
明白了。
OK, here's the plan.
好的，这是计划。
Oh, oh, whoa... No, no.
哦，哦，哇...不，不。
You made the last decision.
你做出了最后的决定。
It's my turn.
轮到我了。
Sure, Patrick,
what do you think we should do?
当然，帕特里克，
你认为我们应该做什么？
Um...
嗯...
Maybe, uh...
也许，呃...
Uh, Patrick...
呃，帕特里克...
Well, for crying
out loud, SpongeBob
嗯，为了哭
大声说出来，海绵宝宝
I didn't rush you
when it was your turn.
我没有催你
当轮到你的时候。
Sorry, sorry,
take your time.
对不起，对不起，
慢慢来。
Ohh...
哦...
Oh, shoot...
哦，射击...
I forgot what
I was gonna say.
我忘了什么
我正想说。
No hurry, Patrick.
不着急，帕特里克。
Do you wanna play
hide and go seek?
你想玩吗
隐藏然后寻找？
Sure.
当然。
Let's go play in
that cave over there?
我们去玩吧
那边那个山洞？
I like it here.
我喜欢这里。
It's roomy...
很宽敞...
And best of all, we have
this cave all to ourselves.
最重要的是，我们有
这个山洞全是我们自己的。
Huh?
啊？
Mice.
老鼠。
We'll only stay here tonight
我们今晚只会留在这里
and then head home tomorrow.
然后明天回家。
Home?
家？
This is your new home.
这是你的新家。
You'll be here forever
你会永远在这里
just like me...
就像我一样...
Good times.
美好时光。
What do you mean,
"We'll be here forever?"
你是什么意思，
“我们会永远在这里吗？”
How long have  you  been here?
你来这里多久了？
40 years, I been here.
40年了，我一直在这里。
There ain't no way
out of this valley.
没有办法
出了这个山谷。
You're stuck here with me
for the rest of your lives.
你和我一起被困在这里
为了你的余生。
We'll be here forever?
我们会永远在这里吗？
We're doomed.
我们注定了。
Are you kidding?
你在开玩笑吧？
That old coot's been here
for years and look at him.
那个老傻瓜来过这里
多年来，看看他。
He's in great shape.
他身体状况很好。
Look at those muscular arms.
看看那肌肉发达的手臂。
His rock-hard abs.
他那坚如磐石的腹肌。
And that great complexion.
还有那出色的肤色。
Why he's glowing with health.
为什么他容光焕发。
You're right, Patrick.
你是对的，帕特里克。
But what will we eat?
但我们要吃什么呢？
Where will we sleep?
我们睡哪儿？
Patrick: Well, I don't
know about you
帕特里克：嗯，我不
了解你
but I've got all the comforts
of home right here.
但我已经拥有了所有的舒适
家就在这里。
Patrick's right.
帕特里克是对的。
If I'm stuck here
I should make the best of it.
如果我被困在这里
我应该充分利用它。
I'll build myself a new home.
我要为自己建造一个新家。
There, just like my pineapple
in Bikini Bottom...
在那里，就像我的菠萝一样
在比基尼底部...
Only smaller.
只是更小而已。
: How comfy.
: 多舒服啊。
Safe and sound
in my own little home.
安全无虞
在我自己的小家里。
Safe?
安全的？
You're never
safe out in the wild.
你从来都不是
在野外安全。
If I were you...
如果我是你...
I'd keep and eye
on that big fella.
我会留意
就在那个大家伙身上。
Patrick?
帕特里克？
Oh, Patrick is
my best friend.
哦，帕特里克是
我最好的朋友。
He wouldn't hurt me.
他不会伤害我。
He's a big boy.
他是个大男孩了。
Out here, till
it's eat or be eaten.
在这里，直到
它是吃或被吃。
He's gotten the taste of flesh.
他尝到了肉的味道。
Hey, Patrick.
嘿，帕特里克。
Hey, SpongeBob.
嘿，海绵宝宝。
Sounds like
you're hungry.
听起来像
你饿了。
Boy, am I.
男孩，我是吗？
I'm so hungry...
我好饿……
I could eat anything.
我什么都可以吃。
I could eat
an entire sponge...
我可以吃
一整块海绵...
...cake.
...蛋糕。
I was just gonna share my
golden sponge cake with him.
我只是想分享我的
金色海绵蛋糕和他在一起。
It's got delicious
cream filling, too.
已经好吃了
奶油馅也可以。
Mmm...
嗯...
It's all true.
这都是真的。
Patrick  is  going to eat me.
帕特里克要吃了我。
What should I do?
我应该怎么办？
You gotta protect yourself.
你必须保护自己。
What you need is a fort.
你需要的是一座堡垒。
This mud replica
of the Krusty Krab
这个泥巴复制品
蟹堡王的
should protect me from
that fiend, Patrick.
应该保护我免受
那个恶魔，帕特里克。
Ah!
啊!
He's on to me.
他对我有兴趣。
Must hide.
必须隐藏。
I'm safe.
我很安全。
Patrick can't get me in here.
帕特里克不能让我进来。
I don't need to go outside.
我不需要出去。
I have everything
I need right here.
我拥有一切
我需要就在这里。
Spatula...
抹刀...
Now I just need some buns.
现在我只需要一些面包。
Oh, crunchy.
哦，脆脆的。
I can't take it!
我受不了！
Ahh!
啊！
I need some real food.
我需要一些真正的食物。
Remember, kid...
记住，孩子...
It's eat or be eaten.
要么吃，要么被吃。
Yes, yes...
是的，是的...
I shall eat Patrick
before he eats me.
我要吃帕特里克
在他吃掉我之前。
Ohh...
哦...
Something smells good.
有些东西闻起来很香。
What are you cooking, SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝，你在做什么菜？
I'm gonna cook
you up and eat ya.
我会做饭
你起来吃吧。
Ah, well, why do
you wanna eat me?
啊，好吧，为什么
你想吃我吗？
I know what you're going.
我知道你要做什么。
You're playing dumb.
你在装傻。
But it won't work
但这行不通
because I'm going to eat you
before you eat me.
因为我要吃了你
在你吃掉我之前。
Well, not if
I eat you first.
好吧，不是如果
我先吃你。
Oh, no, you don't
哦，不，你不
Where'd he go?
他去哪儿了？
Come on out, Patrick.
出来吧，帕特里克。
You can't hide forever.
你不可能永远隐藏。
What's this... Warm water?
这是什么……温水？
You seemed kind of tense
你看起来有点紧张
so I drew you a hot bath.
所以我给你洗了个热水澡。
Well, thanks, Patrick.
嗯，谢谢，帕特里克。
I did get a trifle
unhinged, didn't I?
我确实得到了一点
我精神错乱了，不是吗？
Oops...
哎呀...
I forgot the bath beads.
我忘记了浴珠。
Thanks, Patrick,
you're a real pal.
谢谢，帕特里克，
你是一个真正的朋友。
They almost look like carrots.
它们看起来几乎像胡萝卜。
Carrots?
胡萝卜？
You're making soup
out of me.
你在煮汤
从我身上。
I was not.
我不是。
It was supposed to be stew.
本来应该是炖菜的。
Whew.
呼。
I'm getting tired.
我累了。
Why don't you take a nap
on this nice soft bed.
你为什么不小睡一下
在这张柔软的床上。
There, that's it.
就在那里，就是这样。
Here, I'll tuck you in with
this nice soft blanket.
在这里，我会为你塞上被子
这条柔软的毯子。
And what's a blanket
without a little ketchup?
还有什么是毯子
没有一点番茄酱？
Nee-mee-nee-mee...
妮---------------
This isn't a bed.
这不是床。
Wait, come back.
等一下，回来吧。
SpongeBob: You're not
properly seasoned.
海绵宝宝：你不是
适当调味。
Mmm...
嗯...
Ahh!
啊！
SpongeBob: Ahh!
海绵宝宝：啊！
Patrick: Whoa, hey...
帕特里克：哇，嘿……
Give me that
ketchup back.
给我那个
番茄酱回来。
No.
不。
Got ya.
明白了。
No, got you.
不，明白了。
I got you.
我接到你了。
Congratulations,
you did it.
恭喜，
你做到了。
Did what?
做了什么？
Why earn your
survivalist medals, of course.
为什么要赚取你的
当然是生存奖章。
Only a hardcore survivalist
只是一个铁杆生存主义者
would break down and
nearly eat his best pal.
会崩溃并且
差点把他最好的朋友吃掉。
Why do you care
if we're survivalists?
你为什么关心
如果我们是生存主义者？
'Cause I'm not
just some old hermit.
因为我不是
只是一些老隐士。
I'm Sandy Cheeks,
survivalist extraordinaire.
我是桑迪·奇克斯
非凡的生存主义者。
Sandy?
沙？
It weren't no accident that
you fell out of my truck.
这并非偶然
你从我的卡车上掉下来了。
I was just testing
your survival skills.
我只是在测试
你的生存技能。
You planned this?
这是你策划的吗？
Yup...
是的...
And I'm happy to say
you both passed.
我很高兴地说
你们都通过了。
Here's your survivalist medals.
这是你的生存奖章。
Hooray.
万岁。
Wow, it's great that
we won our medals.
哇，太好了
我们赢得了奖牌。
But I'm still hungry.
但我还是饿了。
Me too.
我也是。
Guys...
伙计们...
What ya doing?
你在做什么？
Uh, fellas?
呃，伙计们？
Eat or
be eaten.
吃或
被吃掉。
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
Next time I'll bring
more granola.
下次我会带
更多格兰诺拉麦片。